Guide to the David Jacks Papers, 1845-1960
Department of Special Collections
- CORRESPONDENCE 1864, Jan.-Mar. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 47. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, Mar. 31, 1864., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1864, Apr.-Jun. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1. Romie, E[rnest] to DJ, Apr. 1. 1864., 2 pp.
  - 2. Jacks, David to [Mary C. Jacks], Apr. 5, l864., 2 pp.
  - 3. Hunt, E.0. to DJ, Apr. 6, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 4. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, Apr. 12, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 5. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, Apr. [12 or 13], 1864., 2 pp.
  - 6. Tompkins, Edward to DJ, Apr. 13, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 7. Haight, Henry H. to W.W. Stow, Apr. 15, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 8. Tompkins, Edward to DJ, Apr. 16, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 9. Unknown to M.C. Briggs, Apr. 20, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 10. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Apr. 21, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 11. Reynolds, Mrs. E.L. to DJ, Apr. 23, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 12. Tompkins, Edward to DJ, Apr. 26, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 13. Ashley, Annie to DJ, May 5, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 14. MacEwan, D. to DJ, May 6, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 15. Flood & 0 'Brien to DJ, May 7, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 16. Ord, James L. to DJ, May 9, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 17. Patterson, _____ to DJ, May 9, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 18. Allen & Spier to DJ, May 10, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 19. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, May 13, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 20. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, May 13, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 21. Ashley, D.R. to DJ, May 16, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 22. Taylor, Alex[ander] S. to DJ, May l8, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 23. Tompkins, Edward to DJ, May 16, 1864., 2 pp
  - 24. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, May 21, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 25. [Taylor, Alexander S.] to DJ, May 26, 1864.(The signature looks like Alex. J. Taylor but the property is A.S.'s)., 4 pp.
  - 26. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, May 27, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 27. Gordon, W[illia]m to DJ, Jun. 14, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 28. Tompkins, Edward to DJ, Jun. 15, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 29. Callaghan, J[ohn] D. to DJ, Jun. 19, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 30. Cool, P. Y. to DJ, Jun. 22, 1864., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1864 Jul.-Sept. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1. McElroy, James R. to Robert McElroy, Jul. 2, 1864., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 2. Phillips, John Burke, Fletcher M. Haight & W. E. Lovett to J. McDowell & George Wright, Jul. 4, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 3. Taylor, Alex[ander] S. to DJ, Jul. 8, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 4. McElroy, Robert to DJ, Jul. 14, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 5. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jul. 18, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 6. Dougall, Cathrine [sic] Sharp to DJ, July 19, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 7. Barr, Sarah A. to DJ, Jul. 23, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 8. Haupmann, H. to DJ, Jul. 25, 1864. 2, pp.
  - 9. Savage, Richard (ptd.) to DJ, Jul. 25, 1864., 2 pp. assessment.
  - 10. Williams, Edw[ard] L. to DJ, Jul. 25, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 11. Flood & 0 'Brien to DJ, Jul. 26, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 12. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Jul. 29, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 13. Parker, W.M.R. to DJ, Aug. 1, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 14. Bannister, E. to DJ, Aug. 5, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 15. Josselyn, A.S. to DJ, Aug. 5, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 16. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Aug. 9, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 17. Jacks, David to Rowland Walker & Co., Aug. 9, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 18. Pierce, _____ to DJ, Aug. 11 1864., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 19. Romie, E[rnest] to DJ, Aug. 11, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 20. Coles, Henry to DJ, Aug. 20, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 21. Flood & 0'Brien to DJ, Aug. 22, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 22. Jacks, David to John Galbraith, Aug. 27, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 23. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Aug. 31, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 24. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, Sept. 1, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 25. Romie, Ernest to DJ, [Sept.] 7, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 26. Meagher, Michael to DJ, Sept. 16, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 27. McElroy, J.R. to DJ, Sept. 20, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 28. Payne,[Bolado S.] to DJ, Sept. 22, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 29. Reynolds, [Harnett], & Ford to M[atthew] C. Ireland, Sept. 22, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 30. Ashley, D.R. to DJ, Sept. 21, 1864., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 31. Simonds, S.D. to DJ, Sept. 24, 1864., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 32. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Sept. 26, 1864., 2 pp. Tel
- CORRESPONDENCE 1864 Oct.-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, Oct. 2, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 2. Woods, F.H. to DJ, Oct 3, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 3. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Oct. 4, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 4. Benson, H.C. to DJ, Oct. 4, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 5. McQuillan, Ja[me]s B. to DJ, Oct. 4, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 6. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Oct 8, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 7. Rowland, R.E. to DJ, Oct. 10, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 8. Romia, C[harles] T. to DJ, Oct. 11, 1864., 2pp.
  - 9. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Oct. 13, 1864., 2 pp. in Spanish
  - 10. Flood & 0'Brien to DJ, Oct. 14, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 11. Jacks, David to Theodore Brown, Oct. 14, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 12. Taylor, Alex[ander] S. to DJ, Oct. 14, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 13. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Oct. 17, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 14. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Oct. 17, 1864., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 15. Ord, J[ames] L. to DJ, Oct. 17, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 16. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Oct. 18. 1864., 4 pp.
  - 17. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Oct. 18, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 18. Haight, Robert to DJ, Oct. 21, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 19. Patterson, _____ to DJ, Oct. 24, 1864.Copy of letter-to Ashley., 3 pp. in Spanish.
  - 20. Brown, The[odore] to DJ, Oct. 30, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 21. Ord, J[ames] L. to DJ, Oct. 30, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 22. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Oct. 30, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 23. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Nov. 1, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 24. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Nov. 3, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 25. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Nov. 7, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 26. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Nov. 12, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 27. Hinds, T.W. to DJ, Nov. 11, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 28. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Nov. 14, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 29. Higgins, Elisha to DJ, Nov. 15, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 30. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Nov. 16, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 31. Stearns, John P. to DJ, Nov. 16, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 32. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Nov. 18, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 33. Mansfield, Nathan F. to _____? Little, Nov. 21, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 34. Sames, L.C. to [?DJ], Nov. 21, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 35. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, Nov. 23, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 36. Sames, L.C. to Unknown, Nov. 23, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 37. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ, Nov. 28, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 38. Hinds, Alfred J. to DJ, Nov. 28, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 39. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Nov. 29, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 40. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Dec. 5, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 41. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Dec. 7. 1864., 2 pp.
  - 42. Ord, J[ames] L. to DJ, Dec. 7, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 43. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Dec. 10, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 44. Walker, Thomas to DJ, Dec. 14, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 45. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Dec. 15, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 46. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Dec. 22, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 47. Patterson. to DJ, Dec. 24, 1864., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 48. Tiffany, Geo[rge] 0. to Flood & 0'Brien, Dec. 26, 1864.sent on to DJ., 2 pp.
  - 49. Armes, G.W. to DJ, Dec. 28, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 50. Taylor, Alex. S. to DJ, Dec. 28, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 51. [Higgins, Elisha] to DJ, Dec. 29, 1864., 3 pp.
  - 52. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Dec. 29, 1864., 4 pp.
  - 53. Moore & Bixby to DJ, Dec. 29, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 54. Josselyn, A. S. to DJ, Dec. 30, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 55. McDougall, A. to DJ, Dec. 30, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 56. Rowland Walker Co. to DJ, Dec. 30, 1864., 2 pp.
  - 57. A[shley, D. R.] to Unknown, [1864]., 1 p.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1865 Jan.-Mar. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jan. 4, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 2. Thornton, S[amuel] K. to DJ, Jan. 5, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 3. Taylor, Alex. S. to DJ, Jan. 7, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 4. Hall, Annie J. to DJ, Jan. 13, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 5. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ, Jan. 20, 1865., 4 pp. 2 same date
  - 6. Soto, J.M. to DJ, Jan. 20, 1865., 3 pp. in Spanish.
  - 7. Wheeler, John 0. to DJ, Jan. 20, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 8. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ, Jan. 27, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 9. Thorn, Thomas to DJ, Jan. 30, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 10. Wain, Col. _____ to [M.C.] Ireland, Jan. 30, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 11. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ, Jan. 31, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 12. Ireland, M.] C. to Badger & Lindenberger, Feb. 1, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 13. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Feb. 3, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 14. Taylor, Alex. S. to DJ, Feb 3, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 15. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ, Feb. 7, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 16. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Feb. 8 1865., 2 pp.
  - 17. Ashley, D.R. to Unknown, Feb. 13, [1865]., 2 pp.
  - 18. Lovett, W.E. to DJ, Feb. 14, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 19. Taylor, Anne to DJ, Feb.14, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 20. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Feb. 16, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 21. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Feb. 16 1865., 2 pp.
  - 22. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Feb. 16, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 23. Taylor, Alex. S. to DJ, Feb. 16, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 24. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Feb. 7, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 25. Smith, Austin to [M.C.] Ireland, Feb. 18, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 26. Lovett, W.E. to DJ, Feb. 19, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 27. Jacks, David to W[illia]m H. Patterson, Feb. 20, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 28. Wheeler J[ohn] O. to DJ, Feb. 20, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 29. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Feb. 24, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 30. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ, Feb. 25, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 31. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Mar. 1, 1865., 2 pp. and clip.
  - 32. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ Mar. 1, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 33. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Mar. 2, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 34. Brown,Theodore to DJ, Mar. 4, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 35. Romie, M[aria F.] to Ernest [Romie], Mar. 3, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 36. Sherwood, Eugene to DJ, Mar. 6, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 37. Taylor, Alx. S. to DJ, Mar. 6, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 38. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Mar. 7, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 39. Gardner, R. to Unknown, Mar. 11, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 40. Thorn, Thomas to DJ Mar.11 1865., 3 pp.
  - 41. Flood & 0'Brien to DJ, Mar. 12, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 42. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Mar. 13, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 43. Brown, Mary J. to Unknown, Mar. 13, 1865., 6 pp.
  - 44. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Mar. 15, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 45. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Mar. 15, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 46. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Mar. 16, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 47. Haight, F[letcherl M. to DJ, Mar. 11, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 48. Tierney, Ed[ward] P. to DJ, Mar. 21, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 49. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Mar. 22, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 50. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Mar. 25, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 51. Newman & Brannan to DJ, Mar. 25, 1865., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1865 Apr.-Jul. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1. Soto, José M. to DJ, Apr. [4], 1865., 3 pp. in Spanish
  - 2. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Apr. 10, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 3. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Apr. 13, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 4. Weygant F.E. to DJ, Apr. 16, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 5. Flood, [J.C.] to DJ, Apr. 18, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 6. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Apr. 20, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 7. Hartman, Isaac to DJ, Apr. 21, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 8. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Apr. 25, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 9. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Apr. 26, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 10. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Apr. 29, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 11. Coles, Henry to DJ, Apr., 1865., 2 pp.
  - 12. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, May 3, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 13. Hooper, W[illia]m to DJ, May 4, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 14. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, May 5, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 15. McQuillan, Ja[me]s B. to DJ, May 6, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 16. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, May 8, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 17. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, May 8, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 18. Higgins, E[lisha] to Lewis Little, May 6, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 19. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, May 9, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 20. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, May 11, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 21. Smith, Benjamin to DJ, May 12, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 22. Ashley, [Annie] to DJ, May 15, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 23. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, May 16, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 24. Headen, B.F. to [?DJ], May 17, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 25. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, May 25, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 26. Ashley, Annie to DJ, May 29, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 27. Ashley, Annie to DJ, May 30, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 28. Barrows, H.D. to DJ, May 30, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 29. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, May 30, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 30. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jun. 5, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 31. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Jun. 5, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 32. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jun. 6, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 33. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Jun. 6, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 34. Rowland, Walker & Co. to DJ, Jun. 6, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 35. Thompson, G. Howard to DJ, Jun. 6, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 36. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jun. 12, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 37. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Jun. 12, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 38. Patterson, Wallace & Stow to DJ, Jun. 12, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 39. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jun. 13, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 40. McQuillan, Jas. B. to Unknown, Jun. 13, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 41. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jun. 14, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 42. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jun. 14, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 43. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jun. 19, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 44. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Jun. 20, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 45. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Jun. 20, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 46. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jun. 23, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 47. Manuel Diaz, Jun. 23, 1865.Copy by C.A. Canfield., 2 pp. order.
  - 48. Cooper, John B.R. to DJ, Jun. 23, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 49. Davidson, Donald to DJ, Jun. 23, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 50. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jun. 24, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 51. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jun. 24, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 52. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jun. 25, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 53. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Jun. 26, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 54. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jun. 28, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 55. Bannister, E[lisha]to DJ, Jun. 28, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 56. Warren & Co. to M.C. Ireland, Jun. 29, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 57. Allen & Spier to DJ, Jun. 30, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 58. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Jul. 1 1865., 2 pp.
  - 59. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Jul. 3, 1865., 4 pp. with 2 notes.
  - 60. Baker, G.R. to DJ, Jul. 3, 1865., 2 pp
  - 61. Galbraith, Johan [sic] to DJ, Jul. 4, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 62. McElroy, Robert to DJ, Jul. 6, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 65. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jul. 7, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 66. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jul. 12, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 67. Jacks, David to Mary [C.] Jacks, Jul. 12, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 68. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Jul. 13, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 69. Higgins E[lisha] to DJ, Jul. 13, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 70. Ord, J[ames] L. to DJ, Jul. 14, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 71. Macdonald, A.C. to Unknown, Jul. 18, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 72. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jul. 21, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 73. Brown, Theodore to DJ, Jul. 23, 1865., 2 pp
  - 74. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Jul. 26, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 75. Curtis, Murray to DJ, Jul. 26, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 76. McElroy, Robert to DJ, Jul. 28, 1865., 2 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1865 Aug.-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ, Aug. 1, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 2. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Aug. 4, 1865., 4 pp. with bill.
  - 3. Blankinship, J.A. to McDougall & Ireland, Aug. 4, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 4. Thompson, G. Howard to DJ, Aug. 7, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 5. Cox, Peter to DJ, Aug. 12, 1865., 1 p. proxy.
  - 6. Cox, Peter to DJ, Aug. 12, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 7. McElroy, Robert to DJ, Aug. 12, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 8. Soto, J[osé] M. to DJ, Aug. 17, 1865., 2 pp. in Spanish.
  - 9. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Aug. 19, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 10. Patton, John W. to DJ, Aug. 20, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 11. Hinds, W[illia]m to DJ, Aug. 21, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 12. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Aug. 23, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 13. Graves, George to DJ, Aug. 23, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 14. Josselyn, A.S. to M.C. Ireland, Aug. 24, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 15. [Somavia] José G. to DJ, Aug. 22, 1865., 2 pp. in Spanish.
  - 15a. Hughes, [Michael?] to DJ, Sept 3, 1865.Misdated 1868 on docket., 2 pp.
  - 16. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Sept. 4, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 17. McDougall, A.C. to DJ Sept. 5, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 18. Headen, B.F. to [?DJ], Sept. 18, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 19. Hal1y, William to Unknown, (David McEwan) Sept. 20, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 20. Hally, William to DJ, Sept. 22, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 21. Macewan, D[avid] to DJ, Sept. 22, 1865., 6 pp.
  - 22. Jacks, David to Ernest Romie, Sept. 26, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 23. Hayden, Geo[rge] W. to W(illia]m Curtis, Sept. 28, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 24. Parks, W[illia]m H. to M.C. Ireland, Oct. 4, 1865., 4 pp.
  - 25. Ashley, D.R. to DJ, Oct. 5, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 26, Slocum, W.N. to DJ, Oct. 9, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 27. Jacks, David to John Myers, Oct. 11, 1865.Certified by Ja[me]s B. Smith, Sheriff of Monterey Co., 2 pp.
  - 28. Smith, David to D. Macewan (?David), Oct. 11, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 29. Ashley, D.R. to DJ, Oct. 12, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 30. Macewan, D(avid) to [DJ], Oct. 12, 1865., 8 pp.
  - 31. Ashley, D.R. to DJ, Oct. 14, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 32. Robson, W[illia]m to DJ, Oct. 17, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 33. McElroy, Robert to DJ, Oct. 10, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 34. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Oct. 24, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 35. Haight and Pierson to [?DJ], Oct. 26, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 36. Slocum, W.N. to [DJ], Nov. 11, 1865,with receipts, and account sheet., 7 pp.
  - 37. Parker, W.M.R. to DJ, Nov. 27, 1865., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 38. Jacks, David to J[ohn] D. Callaghan, Nov. 2-8, 1865., 2 pp.
  - 39. Niman, Geo[rge] W. to M.C. Ireland, Nov., 1865., 2 pp.
  - 40. Higgins, E[lisha]to DJ, Dec. 11, 18651, 2 pp.
  - 41. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Dec. 21, 1865., 2 pp. and clip.
  - 42. Rowland, R.E. to DJ, Dec. 25, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 43. Thorn, Thomas to DJ, Dec. 25, 1865., 3 pp.
  - 44. Abrego, Jose to R.E. Rowland, Dec. 25, 1865., 2 pp. in Spanish
- CORRESPONDENCE 1866 Jan.-Jun. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1. Blasdal, H.G. to Robert McElroy, Jan. 1, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 2. Cool, P.Y. to DJ, Jan. 1, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 3. Fox, Bernard S. to DJ, Jan. 5, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 4. McElroy, Robert to DJ, Jan. 5, l866., 2 pp.
  - 5. Flood, J[ames] C. to DJ, Jan. 6, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 6. Ireland, M[atthew] C. to DJ, Jan. 8, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 7. Hartman, Isaac, to DJ, Jan. 9. 1866., 3 pp.
  - 8. Hartman, Isaac, to DJ, Jan. 12, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 9. Gray, E. to DJ, Jan. 18, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 10. Ireland, M.C. to DJ, Jan. 19, 1866., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 11. Laporte, William to DJ, Jan. 25, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 12. Badger & Lindenberger to M.C. Ireland, Jan. 29, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 13. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Jan. 30, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 14. Fox, Bernard S. to DJ, Feb. 12, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 15. Ireland, M.C. to DJ, Feb. 15, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 16. Jacks, David to Robert Haight, Feb. 17, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 17. Hopkins, R.C. to DJ, Feb. 19, 1866., 4 pp. and note by G. Howard Thompson.
  - 18. Jacks, David to J.M. Soto, Feb. 21, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 19. Fox, B[ernard] S. to DJ, Feb. 22, 1866., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 20. Thorn, Thomas to [M.C.] Ireland, Mar. 2, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 21. Bridge, Sam T. to Unknown, Mar. 6, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 22. Fox, Bernard S. to DJ, Mar. 8, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 23. [Serrano], Florencio et al to W.E. Lovett, Mar. 17, 1866.(docketed Teodoro Gonzales)., 3 pp.
  - 24. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Mar. 20, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 25. Jacks, David to M.C. Ireland, Mar. 29, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 26. Jacks, David to Robert McElroy, Apr. 5, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 27. Ireland, M[atthewl C. to(Edward S. Josselyn], Apr. 9, 1866.
  - 28. Higgins, E[lisha]to DJ, Apr. 28, 1866., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 29. Macewan, D[avid] to DJ, May 8, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 30. Hark[eon], I. to D. Macewan, May 18, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 31. Hartman, Isaac to DJ, May 18, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 32. Henry, Alex[ander] to D. Macewan, May 18, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 33. Langley, John to Walter Muir, May 22, 1866., 2 pp. memo.
  - 34. Jacks, David to John Jefferson, May 25, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 35. Macewan, D[avid] to DJ, May 25, 1866., 12 pp.
  - 36. Rodger, A.M. to [D. Macewan], May 26, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 37. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jun. 6, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 38. McDougall, J[ames] R. Jr. to DJ, Jun. 7, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 39. Jacks, David, to P.Y. Cool, Jun. 15, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 40. Jacks, David to W. Douglass, Jun. 15, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 41. Higgins, E[lisha], to DJ, Jun. 27, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 42. Macewan, D[avid] to DJ, Jun. 29, l866., 4 pp.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1866 Jul.-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Jul. 25, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 2. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Aug. 4, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 3. Jacks, David to Francisco Palacio, Aug. 4, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 4. Unknown to C[ornelius]. [Letter drafted by Jacks to be sent by a third party.] Aug. 8, 1866., 14 pp.
  - 5. Jacks, David to Mary C. Jacks, Aug. 14, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 6. [Jacks, David] to John T. McLean, Aug. 23, 1866., 5 pp. draft.
  - 7. Macewan, D[avid] to DJ, Aug. 23, 1866., 5 pp.
  - 8. Smith [I.] L. to DJ, Sept. 1866., 2 pp.
  - 9. Bralee, Thomas to DJ, Sept. 6, 1866., 2 pp. receipt on verso.
  - 10. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Sept. 12, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 11. Macewan, D[avid] to DJ, Sept. 14, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 12. Hooper, W[illia]m to DJ, Sept. 21, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 13. Kennedy & Hopkins to T.R. Whitcher, Sept. 26, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 14. Slocum, W.N. to B. [Kuffner), Sept. 27, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 15. Slocum, W.N. to DJ, Sept. 28, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 16. Sweett & Gadsby to DJ, Oct. 2, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 17. Hartman I[saac] to DJ, Oct. 9, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 18. Jacks, David to Francisco Palacio, Oct. 10, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 19. Sawyer, Cha[rles] H. to DJ, 19 Oct. 11, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 20. Parker, W.M.R. to M.C. Ireland, Oct. 19, 1866, 2 pp. Tel.
  - 21. Sawyer, C[harles] H. to DJ, Oct. 23, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 22. Donohoe, Kelly & Co. to Flood & O'Brien, Oct. 26, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 23. Jacks, David to Jesus Alonzo, Oct. 30, 1866., 4 pp. incl. copy.
  - 24. McDougall, Mrs. A.C. to Unknown, Oct. 31, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 25. Spence, D[avid] S. to DJ, Nov. 1, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 26. Jacks, David to [Mary C. Jacks], Nov. 3, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 27. Alonzo, Jesus to DJ, Nov. 6, 1866., 2 pp. in Spanish.
  - 28. Jacks, Christian to DJ, Nov. 8, 1866., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 29. Jacks, David to C[ornelius], Nov. 12, 1866 & P.S. Dec. 15., 10 pp.
  - 30. Hartman, I[saac] to DJ, Nov. 19, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 31. Hartman, I[saac] to DJ, Nov. 28, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 32. Jacks, David to [Mary C. Jacks], Nov 29, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 33. Unknown (W.M.S.) to DJ Nov. 30, l866., 2 pp.
  - 34. Jacks, David to [Mary C. Jacks], Dec. 5, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 35. Bridge, Sam T. to DJ, Dec. 6, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 36. McDougall, A.C. to DJ, Dec. 18, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 37. Browne, D. to DJ, Dec. 20, 1866., 5 pp.
  - 38. McLean, J[ohn] T. to DJ, Dec. 24, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 39. Wilson, Jos[eph] to C[.ornelius] Cole, Dec. 26, 1866., 1 p.
  - 39a. Cole, C[ornelius] to [M.C.] Ireland,. [on verso of Wilson to Cole] Dec. 28, 1866., 1 p
  - 40. Newman, C. to DJ, Dec. 26, 1866., 3 pp.
  - 41. Kimball, [Echom] to DJ, Dec. 27, 1866., 4 pp.
  - 42. Jacks, David to Monterey Co. Treasurer, Dec. 28, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 43. Geil, S.F. to DJ, Dec. 29, 1866., 2 pp.
  - 44. Somavia, Jose G. to DJ, Dec. 30, 1866., 2 pp. in Spanish.
- CORRESPONDENCE 1867 Jan.-Apr. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jan. 2, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 2. Jacks, David to John B[urke] Phillips, Jan. 2, 1867., 4 pp.
  - 3. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Jan. 3, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 4. Jacks, David to A. Lewis & Co., Jan. 7, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 5. Hartman, I[saac] to DJ, Jan. 8, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 6. Sawyer, Cha[rle]s H. to DJ, Jan. 10, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 7. Robinson, E.P. to DJ, Jan. 12, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 8. Lewis, A. & Co. to DJ, Jan. 12, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 9. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Jan. 1[3], 1867., 2 pp.
  - 10. Hartman, I[saac] to DJ, Jan. 17, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 11. Jacks, David to Cha[rle]s H. Sawyer, Jan. 19, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 12. Hartman, Isaac to DJ, Jan. 28, 1867., 2 pp. Tel.
  - 13. Taylor, Alex. S. to DJ, Jan. 28, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 14. Flood & O'Brien to DJ, Jan. 29, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 15. Davis & Cowell to DJ, Jan. 30, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 17. Higgins, E[lisha] to DJ, Jan. 30, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 18. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Jan. 30, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 19. Ashton, Cha[rle]s to DJ, Jan. 31, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 20. Holmes, H.T. to DJ, Jan. 31, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 21. Rowland Walker & Co. to DJ, Jan. 31, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 22. Gomez, Juan to DJ, Feb. 5, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 23. Gray, E. to DJ, Feb. 6, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 24. Hinds, J.W. to DJ, Feb. 7, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 25. Chester, A. to DJ, Feb. 8, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 26. Jacks, David to L. Upson, Feb. 8, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 27. Fox, Bernard S. to DJ, Feb. 15, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 28. Beals, J[oseph] R. to DJ, Feb. 16, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 29. Chamberlain & Balch to M.C. Ireland, Feb. 16, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 30. Beals, Jos[eph] R. to DJ, Feb. 18, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 31. Smith, W[illia]m N. to DJ, Feb. 25, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 33. Hunt, E.0. to DJ, Feb. 26, 1867., 2 pp.
  - 34. Ashley, Annie to DJ, Mar. 2, 1867., 3 pp.
  - 35. Hawley, David A. to DJ, Mar. 14, 1867., 2 pp.